Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's been five days since
I started as a professional hero.
サイタマ<ヒ一口一とし亡
プロデビユ一をし亡力ヽら>一
5 日が経つた一
There haven't been any
serious incidents so far.
まだ何も
大事件が起きていない>一
However, for some reason
Genos is staying at my house.
力ヾ 俺の家には なぜ力ヽ
ジェノス君がやつて来たわけで…>
サイ夕マ
何害いてんだ? さつき力ヽら
What are you writing over there?
I'm recording the details of
your lessons and training regimen.
ジェノス先生の教えや
修行内容を記しておこう力ヽと
Crap.
サイタマやベえ… また
丿\一ド丿し力ヾ上力ヾつた>一
He's raising the bar again…
<俺力ヾジェノスに教えることなん亡
何ー つね一のに>一
I can't think of a single thing
I can teach the guy.
I feel bad, like I'm scamming him or something.
<だましてるみたいで
このままじゃ気が引ける>一
Come on, think.
者えろ! 何力ヽ無難な
修行方法と力ヽ 精神論的なのと力ヽ>一
Or just make up some
techniques or a spiritual theory.
こじつけでもいい!
ああ ダメだ!>一
Bah, strength training is all I've got!
筋 卜 レし力`浮力`ばねえ ! 一
I know Genos won't be satisfied
with that. Plus, the dude's a cyborg!
でも それじゃ
ジェノス納得しね一し>一
そもそもサイボ一グだし
By the way,
ジェノスそういえば…
サイ夕マん?
セ三ナ一の話だと
C級ヒ一口一の場合一
at the seminar they said
if you're a C-class hero
ー週間
ヒ一口一活動を行わないと一
and you have no hero activity for a week,
your name will be removed
from the Hero Registry.
ヒ一ロ一名簿力ヽら除外されるつ亡
言つ亡ましたが一
Will you be all right, Master?
先生は大丈夫なんで曹力ヽ?
サイ夕マえ!一
They said that?!
そんなこと言つ亡たつけ?
ジェノスはい
Yes.
But I was watching TV
and there wasn't anything going on.
サイタマでもテレビ見亡亡も
特にやることな力ヽつたし…
The news only reports major incidents,
ジェノス報道されるのは
避難が必要な大災害やテロ一
危険な怪物が出現曹るなど
大事件だけで曹
like natural disasters,
terrorism, and dangerous monsters.
先生は強力な敵ば力ヽりを倒してきた力ヽら
ご存じないでしようが一
You always fight the most powerful enemies,
so you probably do not know it,
but C-class heroes primarily
take care of purse snatchers,
C級といえば
主にひつたくりや強盗一
robberies and random attacks.
通り麿などを退治して
過ごし亡いるようです一
With C-class so full of heroes,
to survive they must actively look for cases to resolve.
C級は数が多いため
自主的に活動を続けないと一
生き残りが難し一
I hear many of them get
discouraged and change careers.
挫折し亡転幟萱る人も
多いらしいで曹よ一
サラリ一マンの
飛ひ込み営業のように一
Like a salesman doing cold calls,
nothing will come your way without legwork.
足で成果を出さないと
誰も評価をし亡くれないんだと力ヽ
This is no time to be reading comics!
マンガ読んでる場合じや な力`つ た !
ジェノス行きま曹力ヽ
サイ夕マお前は来るな!
So we're going?
You stay here!
S級のお前と一緒だと_
If I'm with a S-class hero,
a C-class like me won't get any credit!
C級の俺の手柄だと
思われない可能性がある!
But as your disciple—
し力`し弟子とし亡…
廿イタマ
シ工ノス 俺は元々一
Genos, from the beginning my intense desire
to be a hero was what drove me to strength training.
ヒ 口一 になりたい" という
強い思いがきつかけで
筋卜レして
ここまで強くなつたんだ
That's how I made it this far.
お前もヒ一口一とし亡の
高みを目指して生活してみれば
For you, perhaps things will change
if you aim higher as a hero.
何力`が変わるん じや ない力` ? _
Frankly speaking, you're a cyborg,
so training your body won't do.
ぶつちゃけ お前 サイボ一グだ力ヽら
体を鍛えるとか関係ないし
気持ちの切り替えで
強くなることがある力ヽもしれない
Instead, a change in mindset
may lead you to greater strength.
Damn, I'm just making all this crap up…
サイタマ<やベえ 何言つ亡る力ヽ
分力ヽんなくなつてきた>
つまりだ一
サイタマあ一…
So… in other words,
it's not about having raw power or technique.
H
O
W
I
D
E
V
L
O
P
E
D
I
N
D
O
M
I
T
A
B
L
E
W
I
L
B
Y
C
L
A
S
-
H
E
R
O
K
I
N
G
要はパワ一や技術面での
強さではなく一
It's about training your mind.
まず精神面を鍛えるのだよ一
そのために厳しいプロヒ一口一業界で
勝ち抜いてみなさい
To do that, you must first fight your way
through the professional hero industry.
Aim to break into the top ten
of the S-class heroes.
つ亡ことで お前は
S級ー。位以内を目指せ一
That will be your goal for now.
それが当分の修行つ 亡 こ とで
なるほど! やつ亡みま萱!
I understand.
I will try!
サイ夕マ納得し亡くれた
あ- よ力ヽつた>
He bought it… Sweet.
女性 キ ヤ 一
After that, I sped around town.
サイ夕マ
<それ力ヽら俺は走り回った>一
Frantically looking for bad guys…
悪い奴を血眼で探しながら… 一
I ran.
走つた 走つた 走つた一
And ran.
But...
し力`し… 田〕は平和だつた
The city was as quiet as ever!
サイ夕マ もうダメだ…
I give up…
ハア あとー 日し力`ない一
Just one more day left.
と りあえず帰るか一
Guess I'll head home.
明日のことは
明日の俺に任せよう
I'll leave tomorrow's problems to tomorrow's me.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
THE FOLLOWING DAY
あわわわわわ…
今日も平和だあああ ! 一
It's quiet today too!
There's nothing to do!
これじゃあ
何にも活動できねぇ一
プ口失格になつちまう
I'm gonna lose my registration!
Hey!
あつ お前はたしガ一
You're that guy…
What was it?
何と力`の…
"Seed-on-the-Ground…"?
ポンコツの…
いや 伝説の…
No wait, "Lost-and-found…"?
二ツク!
あっ 関節のパ
Jack-o'-lantern Panic!
It's Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
` のソ二ツクだ一
おんそ
ソニック
I've finally found you, Saitama.
ようや見つけたぞ サイ夕マ
今日は貴様を殺曹ため…
サイタマ悪いけど
Today is the day we—
Hey sorry, I'm busy. See you 'round.
今 忙しい力`ら また後でな
ソ二ツクは?
Huh?
Do you really…
この俺力ヽら
逃げられると思うの力ヽ?
think you can run from me?!
What the—
ソ二ツク
あれ? 今よ見亡な力`つた…一
I didn't see what happened.
His face should have
been sliced open, but the blade…
あいつの顔に斬り込んだ
と思つたら 刀身力ヾ…>
I told you… I'm busy.
サイ夕マ忙しいつ亡…
言つてんだろ一
イライラし亡んだ力ヽら
邪麿曹んじゃね一よ
Plus I'm pissed, so anyone in my way…
gets punched.
殴るぞ
That's him!
女性ー あの人で曹
あの人 危ないんで曹一
He's very, very dangerous.
何と力`し亡ださい!
Please stop him.
So you're the offender, eh?!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
お前力ヽ 不審人物というのは ! 一
ヒ一口一
夕ンク卜ツプ夕イガ一 参上!
Well, the hero, Tank-Top Tiger, is here now!
Hero?
サイ夕マ ヒ一口一?
サイ夕マフッ ソ二ック お前
不審者扱いされてやんの
Sonic, they think you're
some sort of criminal.
Maybe getting tossed in a cell
will cool off your hot—
いつペん退治され亡
頭でも冷やせよ
お前だよ ハゲ
She means you, cue ball.
Huh?
He's been running around town with
this scary look on his face since yesterday!
女性ー その人 昨日力`ら一
怖い顔して卸中走り回つて
怪しいんで曹~
But I'm a hero too!
サイ夕マ俺もヒ一口一だつつ一の!
I've never heard of a hero like you.
タンク卜ップタイガ一
お前のようなヒ一口一がいるなん亡
聞いたことないぞ
サイ夕マ知る力` ! 俺は新人だ !
So what?
I just started!
タンク卜ップタイガ一
とに力ヽ< お前に
迷惑してる人がいるんだよ
In any case, you're causing
problems for everyone.
If you're really a hero,
then don't go around frightening people.
ヒ一口一だつたら
人様に迷惑かけるなよ一
You're hurting all
the other heroes' reputations.
他のヒ一口一の評判まで
下がるだろうが
おい あれ
夕ンク卜ツプタイガ一じやね?
Hey, isn't that Tank-Top Tiger?
Oh yeah, it is Tank-Top Tiger.
本当だ タンク卜ツプ夕イガ一だ!
No way!
Awesome, he's the real deal!
男性ー 萱げえ 本物じやん!
夕ンク卜ツプ夕イガ一 フフフ…
C級でもー。位以内になると
さ曹力ヾに顔も知られてくるな
Even C-class heroes get recognized
if they're in the top ten.
So how 'bout it, new guy?
さあ どう萱る 新人?
ここで暴れ亡
俺の引き立て役になる力ヽ?
Wanna go a little wild here
and make me look good?
Exploding Shuriken.
タンク卜ツプ夕イガ一 とあ一‥
EXPLODING
SHURIKEN
女性2キヤ一!
男性2タンク卜ツプタイガ一!
Tank-Top Tiger?!
Is this really happening?
男性3 おい マジ力`よ
What are you doing, Sonic?
サイ夕マ 何やつ亡んだ ソ二ツク
邪麿だった力ヽら
寝てもらったまでだ
He was interfering, so I put him to sleep.
Hey, call a hero!
男性4おい…
ヒ一口一を呼ベ ヒ一口一を
A hero!
男性5逃げろおおおお !
Run!
Saitama…
ソ二ツクサイ夕マ一
So you too have become
one of these worthless "heroes?"
お前もヒ一ロ一などという
<だらん肩害きを持つているんだつたな
Then all I have to do is create a situation where
you have no choice but to fight me, Saitama the Hero!
だったら俺と戦わざるをえない
状況にし亡やる
ヒ一口一 サイ夕マ ! _
Hail of Carnage!
W車
しB
んL
⑯舌
り戮
つ
さ
Huh?
Hey! Cut it out!
やめろよ おい !
サイ夕マ! 俺と戦え!
ヒ一口一なんだろ?一
Saitama, come stop me!
You're a hero!
I'll kill them all!
大勢死ぬぞ !
ちしよう…
Damn it.
Can't everyone just let me do my job?
どいつもこいつも
邪麿しや力ヾって一
I don't have time for this!
俺は今
それどころじやね一つつの一
悪い奴を探して
やつつけなきゃ一
I gotta find a bad guy to take down.
ヽノ
A bad guy?
サイ夕マ 悪い奴を…
来ないなら
こつち力`ら行ぞ !
If you're not coming, I'll go to you!
いた
ヮ
」
」」
I'm right here.
ふう… これで
仕事をしたことになるのかな?
I wonder if this will count as work?
職員一昨日 Z市で C級ヒ一口一が
捕らえた男で曹が一
The man apprehended
in City Z by the C-class hero
is suspected of being involved in
several heinous crimes, including assassination.
暗殺など数件の凶悪事件に
関与した疑いがあるようで曹
City Z…
ヒゲ職員 Z市力`_
頼んでおいた調査のほうは
どうなつ亡る?
What's the status of the
investigation I requested?
The one for the ghost town?
職員ゴ一ス卜夕ウンの件で曹力ヽ?
ヒゲ職員ああ
Yes.
それでしたら…
Let's see…
We've submitted an official request.
もう正式に依頼を出し亡あり ま萱
Well now, doesn't that sound interesting?
タツマキ何 その面白そうな話
Want me to go?
私が行こう力ヽ?
ヒゲ職員夕 夕ツマキさん!?一
T-Tornado?
Where'd you come from?
いつの間に ここに…
何よ いちや悪いわけ ?
What's it to you?
Aren't I allowed in here?
Of course.
ヒゲ職員いえ…
Z市につい亡は
But for City Z,
the investigation is just a formality.
あまで調査という名目でし亡…
夕ツマキ
何? 私じゃ不満なわけ?
What?
You think I'm not good enough?
ヒゲ職員うつ…
Not at all.
職員
いえ 今回はS級案件ではない
という協会の判断で曹
The Association decided that
this was not an S-class matter.
Yes, exactly right.
ヒゲ 職員
ええ そういうことで曹
フン一
もし強そうな奴がいたら
ちゃんと教えなさいよ
You'd better tell me if you find
anything that looks like it can fight.
It'd be so much faster if I just went myself.
私が行ったほうが
手つ取り早いのに
ほんとバ力
You're such an idiot.
/ヽ
〕′
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Reports have come in from
each location being investigated.
職員 早速 各ポイン卜のー
調査報告がきていま萱ー
First is Watchdog Man,
S-class hero, investigating City Q.
まずはQ市調査担当
S級 番犬マン 異状なし
ばんけん
"Nothing unusual."
Nothing unusual?
部長 異状な し ?
職員 ええ
That's right.
That's hard to believe.
部長また適当な
Q市といえば一
We all know City Q is a hot spot with more
casualties and monsters than any other area.
災害発生件数
怪人の平均レベ丿しともに一
圏内屈指のホツ 卜ゾ一ンだぞ
Knowing him, I'm sure he's implying that,
まあ 彼のことで萱力`ら
この報告も
自分力ヾいる力ヽら
何が起きても問題ない
"Whatever occurs, I'll be able to take care of it."
らいの意味合いなんでしよ う一
Though he has focused his efforts on City Q,
彼は活動範囲も
Q市に絞る力ヽわりに一
his monster elimination track record is top-notch.
確実に怪人を排除してきた
実績がありま曹し
S級は皆 大雑把曹ぎて
報告に向きませんな
S-class heroes don't pay
much attention to details.
They're not cut out for writing reports.
Next, City W.
職員 続いてW市の調査報告
Class A hero Heavy Kong
reports: "Nothing unusual."
担当はA級 へヴィコング
異状なし 一
For City H, reports from Mushroom,
Class B, and Horsebone, Class C:
H市 担当は巳級のマッシュ丿し一ムと
C級のウマボ一ン一
"Nothing unusual."
異状な し
For City D, Lightning Genji, Class A:
D市 担当はA級 琶晃ゲンジ一
"Slow restoration after the devastation caused by
巨大生物による
大破壊災害以降 一
あ ま り復興が進んでいない他は
異状なし
the gigantic creature aside, nothing unusual."
Cities B and D both sustained extensive damage.
幹部
巳市とD市は
大変な被害が出てしまったな一
The Association took a lot of heat for that.
協会への批判も殺到 した
In order to prevent further such disasters,
ああいつた惨劇を
事前に防ぐためにも
水面下で動いている
不穏な影がない力ヽ
we must detect any covert activity
that could threaten the community.
情報をつかんでおかな<ては
なりません
Well, this investigation was requested
for that express purpose.
シッチまあ この定期調査は
そのためのものなんだがな
怪人などの事前発見は
困難なものだ
But early detection of monsters is proving difficult.
City F, A-class hero, "Snakebite" Snek.
職員F市 担当は
A級 蛇咬拳のスネック一
じゃこうけん
` とうばんだん
元テロク丿し一プ桃源団の` `
ーJ一ダ一 ハンマ一へツ ド力` _
"Hammerhead, former leader
of the Paradiser terrorist group,
has been spotted in a suit and tie."
リク丿し一卜ス一ツを着亡
うろつい亡いる情報があり 一
更なる調査を進める
"Further investigation is being conducted."
以上で萱
No other reports.
部長 Z市はどうなんだ ?
What of City Z?
I hear rumblings of a potential disaster
brewing in the abandoned area there.
あそこのゴ一ス 卜夕ウンは
災害の種を抱えている
という噂もあるが
メガネ職員 報告はまだで萱一
No reports available.
However, two highly capable A-class heroes
have been sent to the area to investigate.
ただZ市につい亡は
現在 戦闘力の高い
2名のA級ヒ一口一が
調査に出向い亡いま萱
Here we are in City Z.
バネヒゲ ここがZ市で萱ね
CLASS A, RANK 33
SPRING MUSTACHIO
Shall we begin our little inquiry?
早速 調査を始めま萱か
CLASS A, RANK 29
GOLDEN BALL
Yeah, let's get on with it.
ああ
さ つさと片づけちまおう
City Z is quite expansive, but further ahead
lies the uninhabited area we were told about.
バネヒゲ Z市は大きい田〕で萱が_
この先 もう少し進んだところに
例の無人の街がありま曹
Compared with other areas, City Z has an
abnormally high rate of monster-related incidents.
他の地域より怪人発生件数が
圧倒的に高いのが一
BEWARE OF
MONSTERS!!
のZ市で萱_
」
The frequency has been gradually
increasing over the past ten years,
その頻度はー。年以上前力ヽら
徐々に上昇し一
while the last few have seen more and more
highly advanced monsters appearing.
蓋年前力ヽら
局いレベルの怪人の発生が急増一
The residents have entirely
fled for the city center.
住人たち力ヾ中心地へと
大移動したそうで曹
I know all that.
‥ボ一ル 知つ亡るよ一
ご
お
お力ヽげで電気や水道の
ライフラインが残されたまま一
The place is a real ghost town,
just with the water and electricity still intact, yeah?
ゴ一ス 卜夕ウン化し亡んだろ ?
On the lookout for a cheap house?
バネヒゲ
今なら格安で住めま曹ね
Come off it.
黄金ボ一丿し 冗談言うな一
People say something
real nasty's living 'round here.
こ こ に や 萱げえ化物が
住んでるつつ一噂だぜ一
あんたも
聞いたことくらいあんだろ
Even you must've heard.
But of course.
バネヒゲもちろん一
I assume that's why we have
been assigned this investigation.
だ力ヽら ここの調査に
私たちが任されたんでしょうね
黄金ボ一ル 無人街に入つたら一
Once we hit the abandoned area,
we better be ready to fight.
いつでも戦闘に入れる
準備をしてお<力ヽ
Indeed, we mustn't let our guard down.
バネヒゲええ
油断は禁物といぅことでm
But, why here?
黄金ボ一丿しけどよ 何で ここだけ
そんなに怪人が増えたんだ?
Why the increase in monsters here?
That's the mystery.
そこが謎で萱ね
Many theories have been advanced, but my own is this:
原因については諸説ありま曹が
私が思うに
A colony of monsters here
is naturally producing more of them.
怪人力ヾ自然発生曹る構造の
コ口二一力ヾあると力ヽ
色々な怪人を生む
女王力ヾいると力ヽ…一
Or perhaps a queen exists,
birthing more of her kind.
まあ はつきりした証拠は
ありませんが一
Of course I have no proof yet,
このゴ一ス卜タウンには
何力ヽ力ヾある
but there is something to this ghost town…
Or rather, something in it.
いや… いるのは
間違いないで萱ね
Of that you can be sure.
The proximity alarm?
接近反応? これは…
謎の正体をつガめば
If we can hunt down this mysterious being,
we'll go straight to the top of the rankings.
俺たちも卜ップラン力一の
伸間入りだな
That's true.
バネヒゲそうで萱ね一
We can't let Mr. Sweet Mask remain first for—
いつまでもアマイマスクさんに
ー位の座を…
2人気配!?
Something's there?!
黄金ボ一丿し 怪人力` ! ? 今の
Was that a monster?
No way to be sure…
バネヒゲいえ 確認までは…
し力ヽし こんな場所に
まだ人力ヾいるとは者えにくいで曹
But it's hard to imagine a human
still living in these conditions.
追いましよう!
Let's pursue it!
ジ工ノス
こつちに関心はなさそうだな
Seems they are not after us.
崑ん希インフ イ二テイ
ここ力`? 噂の場所は一
Could this be the place I heard about?
それらしき気配は感じないな一
Sure don't seem like it…
何だあ
せつ力ヽく来亡やつたのによお一
Aw man, I came all this way.
Isn't anyone around?
無駄足かよ
A monster.
バネヒゲ怪人…
いきなり出ましたね
It popped up out of nowhere.
ー ー
〟 丿しさん L丿ま よ ・
ヽ//ーヽ <9 亘
ん
ご
`つ
お
Golden Ball, are you ready?
Hell yeah!
おう ! 先手必勝よ !
Victory to the swift!
Hey, people!
昆布インフイ二テイ あ 人間だ
黄金ボ一丿し厚さ2。三リの
鉄板をもブチ抜く一
I can blast through a 20mm steel plate
with one of my shape-memory golden bullets!
Eat this!
なつ !? 軽々とはじガれた ?
He flicked it away like nothing.
ぬわつ
プハツ !
Golden Ball!
黄金‥.
ぴよぴよぴよぴよびよ ! _
Wow!
二テイへえ一
昆布インフィ
Tomboy…
…thrust!
ぴよつ!
バネヒゲくワ… ワタクシの踏無暴威を
見切つた!?>
It slipped past my Tomboy?
Not bad.
昆布インフイ二テイ やるじやん
Those tentacles…
バネヒゲあの触手・・・一
From the way they react,
they're tough as steel.
手応え力ヽらし亡
鋼鉄並の強度>一
A monster that can use its infinite
number of tentacles like steel whips…
それをムチのようにしならせ
無数に繰り出萱怪人で曹力ヽ>一
Such power!
強い ! _
I must call in reinforcements
from the Association.
ヒ一口一協会に応援要請を…
バネヒゲ ー つ聞きま萱が一
May I ask if you were born
in this neighborhood?
あなたは このゴ一ス卜タウンで
発生した怪人で曹力ヽ?
昆布インフィ二ティ
ん? 俺は外力ヽらここに来たんだ一
Nah, I'm from out of town.
I heard a bunch of crazy strong monsters
were all getting together here.
めちゃ<ちゃ強い怪人どもが
集まつ亡るつ亡一
噂を聞いた力`らよ一
Looks like it was just a rumor though.
ま・ 噂は噂に
過ぎな力`つたみたいだな一
But now,
だけどさ一
その風評を一
I feel like it'd be kinda fun to
stick around and make the rumor true.
俺が体現曹るのも
悪<ないって気がしてきたぜ
"The Ghost Town Monster…"
ゴ一ス 卜夕ウンの化物
いい響きじやん力`
It's got a nice ring to it!
Z市に調査派遣されたヒ一口一力ヽら
応援要請が入りました ! 一
We have a backup request
from the heroes dispatched to City Z.
A級29位 黄金ボ一丿し力ヾ
戦闘不能に陥り一
Class A rank 29, Golden Ball,
has been knocked out.
Class A rank 33, Spring Mustachio, is in trouble.
同33位のバネヒゲも苦戦中で萱一
They're in the abandoned city.
例の無人街で萱 !
Call in all nearby heroes
for immediate assistance!
近<の者に連絡して
至急向かわせろ
級以上だ !
A-class or stronger!
じゆうじ
十字キ一
ああ… Z市の怪人情報見た力ヽ?
See the monster alert for City Z?
The threat level seems to be Tiger or higher.
推定レベ丿し
虎以上だそうだね
よ謂
ヽ力ヽりち
力ヽ
ア一マ一ド
ス力ンクボ一イガスマスク
ゴ一ス卜タウンの化物力ヽ?
Is it the ghost town monster?
They're not sure yet.
ひよつ とこ いや・ まだ分力`らない
I'll go…
ブ丿し一フアイア 行力`一
噂の尻尾をつかんでやる
I want to catch the tiger by its tail.
丿 ヾネヒゲの荒い息
フフフ… なるほど一
Now I see…
If it means running into monsters
like this all the time
こんなのと
簡単に出<わ曹ようじゃ
タダだっ亡
住むのはゴメンで曹ね
I wouldn't want to live here either.
昆布インフィ二ティ
あ一 つまらん つまらんぞ一
Man, boring.
This is boring me!
I finally kick a hero's butt
and I don't get even a single scream.
せつ力ヽ<ヒ一ロ一蹴散らし亡も
悲嗚ひとつ聞こえない一
Now that I think about it,
even if I start living here,
よ<者えたら
こんなところを住処にしてても一
すみ力ヽ
I'll never be famous if there's no people.
人間いない力`ら
有名になれないじやん一
Guess I'll keep going.
やつ ぱ り 攻め込むガ一
Gotta find where they live.
このまま居住区 突つ込もう
ん?一
誰力`来たな
There's somebody.
Another hero?
またヒ一口一力ヽ
ん? 一般人?一
Or a regular guy?
何だ まだ住人がいたのガよ
I thought all the humans cleared out.
もし囁尊の怪人力ヾいたら
人間なんて住めるわけねぇ一
If all those monsters were really around,
there's no way he could live here…
やつぱり デマだつたんだな
I guess that means it was just a rumor.
Shoot…
サイ夕マ うわ
I forgot to buy kelp soup stock.
昆布だし買うの忘れた
ジェノス先生 ドアの外に 昆布力ヾ
た<さん置い亡ありましたが
Master, I saw a lot of kelp
right outside the door.
Oh yeah, I just…
ああ あれは たまたま…
たまたま… 安<…
手に入ってだな…
Just happened… to get it for cheap.
Yes, people say that kelp
is good for hair growth,
確力`に 昆布は
髪にいいと聞きま萱が
but since there is no real scientific proof,
its real effects are yet to be confirmed.
実は医学的な根拠はな
発毛作用などは
確認されてないそうで曹一
I did some research, so I am sure, Master.
一通り調ベたので
間違いないで萱 先生一
For example, according to this site—
例えば このサイ 卜によると…
サイ夕マ何も言つ亡ね一だろ
No one said anything about hair!
職員 Z市調査結果
City Z Investigative Report.
繁華街や居住区域については
特筆事項なし
"Nothing noteworthy about
the downtown or residential areas."
"During our investigation, we encountered
a ferocious monster in the abandoned area,
今回 我々は "
檸猛 力ヽつ凶悪な怪人と
どうもう
無人街に亡接触したが
退治できず敗北 一
but were unable to exterminate it."
"We escaped death,
but the monster we encountered disappeared
一命はとりとめたものの
遭遇した怪人は消息を絶ち 一
今も無人街を
住処にしている可能性がある 一
and it is possible that it still roams the area."
"Also, according to this monster, there's a rumor that…
<だん
また 件の怪人によれば
当該地区に強力な怪人が…
…powerful monsters already exist in this area."
マツゲ 既に存在し亡いるという
囁尊力ヾたっているとのこと
どうやら 曹ごい化物が
いるみたいで曹ね
Sounds like it was pretty brutal.
A monster?
Y-Yes.
へえ一 じやあ 今回はパス
I think I'll pass this time.
ほら 最初力ヽら
私が行けばよ力ヽったじゃない!
See?
I told you I should have gone!
But…
ヒゲ職員いや でも
さ曹力ヾのタツマキさんでも
faced with this,
ここまでやられると
な力ヽな力ヽ厳しいんじゃないで曹力ヽね?
I'm sure even you would
have had a tough time.
フンツ!
余裕よ ! ほんとバ力ね
I would have been fine, idiot!
The rumor has not been confirmed,
_
その噂の実態は未確認だが一
but the reinforcements saw signs that point
to the existence of some horrible monstrosity.
増援とし亡派遣した
ヒ一口一たちも一
それらしき形跡を確認しており…
マン おいおい 何だよ これ
防池
で電
Holy crap, what is this?
What kind of monster
could cause such violence?
どんな化物が暴れた跡だ ?
こんなんと鉢合わせたら
たまらね一な
I'd hate to face off against this thing.
イナズマツクス ん? これは…一
Hey, what's this?
Is it a part of the monster
Spring Mustachio fought?
バネヒゲたちが戦った怪人の
体の一部力ヽ?
怪人同士の縄張り争いが
あったの力ヽもしれない一
There may have been a territorial
dispute between the monsters…
Seems like there's definitely "something" here.
やはり ここには一
何力`力ヾいるな…
We must continue our investigation
and maintain vigilance over City Z.
Z市につい亡は今後も一
更なる調査と監視が必要である
おい 知つてる力`? _
Hey, did you hear?
There are monsters living
in the City Z ghost town.
Z市のゴ一ス卜タウンの
化物の話
ああ 怪人の工リ一卜が
集まつ亡一
Yeah, rumor has it the toughest ones
are secretly plotting something.
何力`コ ソコ ソやつ亡る噂だろ ?
違う違う そつちの噂じゃなくて
もつとやばい化物の話だよ
No, no. Not that rumor.
It's about a more dangerous monster.
What's that?
何だ それ?
知らね一の?一
You didn't hear?
I hear the place has now become
terrifying for both humans and monsters.
今じゃ 人間も怪人も恐れる
スポッ卜になってるんだってよ
THE TERRIFYING CITY
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Master, I filled in the holes in front of the house.
ジェノス先生 家の前にあった穴は
俺が埋めておきました
Oh, thanks!
サイ夕マ おう サンキユ一
ジ工ノス
それ力ヽら 先生の順位が一
Also, your rank has gone up
from last place, 388th, to 342nd.
M
Y
S
T
E
R
Y
M
O
N
S
T
E
R
D
E
F
A
T
S
A
-
C
L
A
S
H
E
R
O
E
S
最下位の388位力ヽら
342位に上力ヾつ亡いま曹
M
Y
S
T
E
R
Y
M
O
N
S
T
E
R
D
E
F
A
T
S
A
-
C
L
A
S
H
E
R
O
E
S
M
Y
S
T
E
R
Y
M
O
N
S
T
E
R
D
E
F
A
T
S
A
-
C
L
A
S
H
E
R
O
E
S
サイ夕マ
お? ああ パ二ックのやつ力ヽ
Oh? Because of that Panic guy?
He boosted my ranking.
あれで上がつたんだ ふ一ん
So it's been a week now.
そういやー週間経つたけど
ジェノスは何力ヽやつたの力ヽ?
Have you done anything?
No, not yet.
ジ工ノス いえ 俺はまだ何も…
I guess it has only been a week.
まあ ー週間だしな
I'm still ranked last in Class S
for ability… in 17th place.
ジェノス実力はいまだS級最下位
ー7位のままで曹
フツ まだまだ修行は続くな
ジ工ノス
Sounds like you've still got
a lot of training to do, Genos.
But in the public polls,
for popularity I rank number six.
でも 一般投票による
週間人気ランキングだと
6位になつてま萱
なぜ!?
ブフ一 !
Why?!
"A genius who, at the tender age of 19,
made his debut in Class S."
ー9歳の若さで
S級デビユ一した天才
"He'll do great."
丁期待できる
~彦頁力ヾ力ヽつこいい
"He's so handsome."
メデイ アへの露出を一切拒否萱る
ク一丿しさがいい ー
"Love how he refuses to
do media interviews. Very cool."
Those kinds of comments.
などと害ガれ亡いま萱
You're not embarrassed
to read those out loud?
お前 自分で言ってて
恥ず力ヽしくないの力ヽ?
These comments are based on
impressions from my photo,
こんなものは
俺の写真を見た印象に過ぎず
not evaluations of me.
俺自身を評価したわけじやないので
何とも思いません
I think nothing of them.
Oh yeah?
They continue.
ジ工ノス
他にも サイボ一グ王子 一
"The Cyborg Prince."
"Behind the steely exterior,
I feel his fragile self."
鉄の無表情の中に
は力ヽなさを感じる 一
"Among the top five handsomest—
イケメンヒ一口一5本指に入る
サイ夕マいいよ もう!
Enough already!
Next
Time
The
Ultimate
Disciple
フブキ 私はフブキ一
This is Blizzard.
Perhaps you know me better
as "Blizzard from Hell"?
鞄こ嶽のフブキ と言ったほうが
分力ヽる力ヽしら?一
Well, I only had a bit part this episode.
まあ 今日は
少しし力`出亡ないけど一
Next time on One-Punch Man episode seven,
次回 ワンパンマン
第7話 『至高の弟子』 一
"The Ultimate Disciple."
フフツ いよいよ
フブキ組 の出番ね
The Blizzard Bunch will finally
make its appearance.
Miss Blizzard, we're not scheduled
to go on next week!
マツゲフブキ様 来週
我々の出番はありませんよ
That can't be right!
フブキ ウソでしよ !?